savoo.co.uk 2015-11-17

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Statement**

We at Savoo.co.uk (“Savoo”) respect your privacy and value the relationship we have with you. Your visit to this website is subject to this Privacy Policy and its [Terms and Conditions](http://www.bobbibrowncosmetics.com/customer_service/terms.tmpl).

This Privacy Policy describes the types of personal information we collect at Savoo, how we may use that information and with whom we may share it. Our Privacy Policy also describes the measures we take to protect the security of this information as well as how you may reach us to update your contact information or ask us any questions you may have about our use of your personal information.

Please note that this Privacy Policy governs only information provided to Savoo. If you link to another website from this website, you are subject to the privacy policy applicable for that website and we suggest that you consult such privacy policy. This Privacy Policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

**P3P**

Savoo is in compliance with the current draft of the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) Platform for Privacy Preferences (P3P) specification, [ _http://www.w3c.org/P3P_](http://www.w3c.org/P3P), dated April 16, 2002. This specification was developed to allow users to more easily evaluate the use of personal information collected by the web sites they visit. Thus, if your browser is Microsoft Internet Explorer Version 6, or later, your browser can electronically interpret the P3P version of our privacy policies.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**Collection and use of Personal Information**

Providing personal information is voluntary. Savoo will collect and use personal information about you to respond to your request for products and services offered through this website. We will also collect information in order to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. Once you register with Savoo and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. The information we collect may be from the following sources:

  * Information provided by you in connection with obtaining financial products or services such as mortgage loans (such as full name, telephone number, and self-assessed property value).
  * Information you provide us when you register for a user account to receive communications from us (such as your email address).
  * Information you provide us when you enter promotions or sweepstakes offered by Savoo or our co-branded/partnership sites (such as your full name, physical address and email address).
  * Information you provide us through surveys, feedback, or other forms hosted on our website or the pages of a Savoo partner/affiliates.
  * Information you provide us when you select a charity

We also collect demographic information. Demographic information is all other information such as gender, zip code, or any information that is not tied to your personal information. In addition, we might receive information about you from other sources (such as service providers) for tracking purposes. We may add the information we receive about you to your existing account. Like other websites, we also automatically receive and record certain types of information every time you visit us. We use “cookies” and the other information to enhance your experience and present you with personalized offers. See “Cookies and IP Addresses” section below.  
**  
With whom your Information may be shared**

Savoo does not sell trade or rent your personal information to other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

**Service Requests or Loan Products**  – If you submit a request for a loan product or service offered through this website we will share the personal information contained in your request form, such as your full name, physical address, telephone number, property location and self-assessed value, with lenders in our provider network strictly to process and fulfill your request. All lenders in our provider network, which include banks, mortgage lenders and brokers, have entered into marketing agreements with Savoo and are required to comply with federal and state privacy regulations. The lenders may contact you by telephone, email, or mail based on the information you provided to us in order to process and fulfill your request, even if you have opted into the National Do Not Call List administered by the Federal Trade Commission or any state equivalent Do Not Call List. If one of the lenders contacts you by telephone and you wish not to be contacted again by that lender with respect to your inquiry, then you should specifically make a request to that lender not to contact you again. If the lender disregards your request and contacts you again, please let us know immediately by sending an email to Savoo [ _Customer Service_](http://savings.zendesk.com/home). Please note that the lenders may maintain the information you provided whether you elect to use their services or not.

**Other Service or Products Requests**  – If you submit a request for a product or service other than a loan such telecommunication service, we will share the personal information contained in your request form such as your full name, telephone number and email address with our business partners to process and fulfill your request. Our business partners may contact you by telephone, email, or mail based on the information you provided to us, even if you have opted into the National Do Not Call List administered by the Federal Trade Commission or any state equivalent Do Not Call List. If one of our partners contacts you by telephone and you wish not to be contacted again by that business partner with respect to your inquiry, then you should specifically make a request to that partner not to contact you again.

**Vendors**  – We sometimes disclose the information we collect to companies that host certain services for us such as marketing distribution services on our behalf. These vendors only have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, and may not share it with others or use it for any other purpose. These companies are subject to confidentiality agreements with us and other legal restrictions that prohibit them from using the information except to market the specified Savoo products or services.  
**  
As Permitted by Law**  – We may be required to share your personal information with law enforcement or government agencies in response to subpoenas, court orders, federal/state audits or similar circumstances. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Savoo’s Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

**Business Transfer  **– As with any other business, it is possible that Savoo, Inc. in the future could merge with or be acquired by another company. If such an acquisition occurs, the successor company would have access to the information maintained by Savoo, including customer account information, but would continue to be bound by this privacy policy unless you consent otherwise. We will provide notice in this instance as defined in our “Changes to this Privacy Policy” section below.

**Cookies and IP Addresses –  **To serve you faster and with better quality, we use “cookies” technology. Cookies are small bits of code, usually stored on a user’s computer hard drive, which enable a Web site to “personalize” itself for each user. We generally use cookies to reduce the time it takes for pages to load on your computer and to assist with customer tracking. Customer tracking (or “click-stream”) data collected by us is used to optimize your experience by learning whether or not you successfully used Savoo. Cookies are not tied to your personal information. Additionally, we may capture click-stream data on some of our partner’s web sites, limited to the activity involved with the completion of offers listed on our web site This information is used to monitor the performance of our partners. We also allow select third-parties to set cookies on our website. For example, we use a tracking service, Revenue Science, that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about our visitors. This aggregate visitor usage information collected on Savoo and used by the Revenue Science network for the purposes of delivering relevant advertising to our audience. Other examples include session cookies when accessing the Blog section of the website. These cookies simply track the session and are not tied to your personal information. We also keep track of Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP Address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer every time you log on to the Internet.

**Clear Gifs**

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs) that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movement of Web users. Clear gifs are not tied to users’ personally identifiable information. We also use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails the recipients have opened. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If users would like to opt-out of these emails, please see the Opt-out section within any email you receive from us or unsubscribe from our homepage. ** **

**Confidentiality and Security**

The security of your personal information is very important at Savoo and we take a number of steps to safeguard it. For example: We limit access to personal information to those employees or agents who assist us in providing requested products and services to you. Employees are required to comply with our strict policies and procedures regarding the handling of your personal information. Employees who violate these policies are subject to our normal disciplinary process. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard personal information about you. We use industry standard data encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data on the Savoo website.

**Message Boards/Chat Rooms/Blogs**

If you use a message board, chat room, or blog on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

**Third Party Links**

This Privacy Policy applies to all information that you provide to Savoo. However, when you visit websites to which Savoo provides a link, keep in mind you will be interacting with a third party that operates under its own privacy and security policy. If you choose to obtain certain services through a third party site, the data collected by the third party is governed by that third party’s privacy policy. A third party site will also have its own policy regarding the use of cookies and clear gifs. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services.

If Savoo receives personal information from a third party that is not in conjunction with a service offered on our site, the use and disclosure of such information is governed by the agreement (if any) between Savoo and such third party.

**Framing**

In some cases, we may use third party vendors to operate portions of the Savoo website. Although the particular section of the website may have a similar appearance as the Savoo site, information submitted through these outside third parties are subject to this Privacy Policy unless otherwise stated. For example, personal information submitted through our Affiliate Program is subject to our Affiliate Program operator’s privacy policy.

**Children**

We are committed to protecting the privacy of children. Savoo’s services are not written, intended, or designed for children under the age of 13. We do not collect personal information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13.

**Updating your Information**

If you want to access or update the personal information you submitted to Savoo, please contact [_Customer Service_](http://savings.zendesk.com/home). In the alternative, you can write us at the address below and request that your personal information be updated.

**Questions and Suggestions**

If you have any questions, concerns or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, you may contact [ _Customer Service_](http://savings.zendesk.com/home), or you can send a letter to:  
Savoo UK Ltd,  
Attn: Customer Service  
First Floor  
77 St John Street  
Clerkenwell, London EC1M 4NN ** **

**Retention of Information**

Any information we collect may be retained for an indeterminate period of time. Certain detail, particularly sensitive data such as financial information, is only maintained until it is successfully transferred to the partner doing the service fulfillment.

**Who is collecting your Information**

Unless otherwise noted, your information is being collected solely by Savoo. See the Section titled “With whom your information may be shared” above concerning the circumstances under which certain of your information may be disclosed to third parties.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

All versions of this privacy policy are dated with the effective date (the date on which the policy was posted to Savoo) Savoo will only use the information we learn about you in the manner described in the Privacy Policy in effect when the information was collected from you. However, we reserve the right to change the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time by posting revisions to our site. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**Effect of Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or legal rights in or on behalf of any party. As noted above, we may revise this privacy policy from time to time in our sole discretion.

**Effective Date October 18th, 2005**

**Last updated on August 28th, 2015**
